<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1. Shaking Out The Numb on Quantized Crow</title>
    <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1. Shaking Out The Numb on Quantized Crow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shaking Out the Numb</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/1/musicalbum/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/1/musicalbum/</guid>
      <description>A still from the video for Free. Copyright 2020 Loma Vista Recordings.
  
To put it concisely, Sylvan Esso are a savvy artistic duo composed of Amelia Meath and Nick Sanborn. The project is the marriage of Meath&amp;rsquo;s silken vocals with Sanborn&amp;rsquo;s gravelled synth. Sometimes her voice is shattered and interspliced, other times it is allowed to ebb and flow around the electronic instrumentals. Freedom and structure are intertwined like ice water passing through a glacier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Berman and the Necessity of Levity</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/1/musicsingle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/1/musicsingle/</guid>
      <description>A still from the video for Darkness &amp;amp; Cold
  
The first songs I heard from David Berman were the singles released in advance of his Purple Mountains project. It shone like dark neon; the songs dazzled as they whirled between bleak honesty and being honestly bleak. It was clear that he was wrestling with despair but still managed to find humour in the depths of it all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life in the Clouds of Hell</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/1/scienceheadline/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/1/scienceheadline/</guid>
      <description>An image captured by the Hinode spacecraft of the 2012 transit of Venus. Copyright JAXA/NASA.
  
Nobody knows who discovered Venus, our celestial neighbour and the second planet from the Sun, it&amp;rsquo;s been a feature of human culture since time immemorial. Its scientific name is an artifact of the Roman association of the planet, which they called Luciferus, with the goddess of beauty, Venus. In the first half of the 20th century, books like C.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
