<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2. Supermassive Heart of Darkness on Quantized Crow</title>
    <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2. Supermassive Heart of Darkness on Quantized Crow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rubber Bullets For The Clown</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/2/musicalbum/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/2/musicalbum/</guid>
      <description>A still from the video for Sparkle Hard: The Movie.
  
In 2018, Stephen Malkmus released what I rate as a near-perfect album, Sparkle Hard, his seventh with The Jicks. If you know Malkmus, it&amp;rsquo;s likely that you&amp;rsquo;re aware of Pavement. Pavement were a quintessential sound of the 90&amp;rsquo;s, and Stephen Malkmus was the nucleus of that project. I imagine it must be super annoying to have work you produced several decades ago referenced in every new release, so let&amp;rsquo;s move on from Pavement and talk about Sparkle Hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>...A Thought Half-Forms</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/2/musicsingle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/2/musicsingle/</guid>
      <description>Cover art for Postcard from Spain.
  
Anderson .Paak raised a fist earlier this year and crystalised our moment in history with the most powerful track of 2020: Lockdown. Two weeks ago, he returned with JEWELZ. It&amp;rsquo;s a fun track, the slapping bass and vocoder produce a feel that would&amp;rsquo;ve allowed it to comfortably slip into a playlist for the summer we never had. JEWELZ is contrasted by my next pick, I&amp;rsquo;ve Made Up My Mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supermassive Heart of Darkness</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/2/scienceheadline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/2/scienceheadline/</guid>
      <description>Composite infrared image of the center of our Milky Way galaxy, which spans over 600 light-years. Credits: NASA/SOFIA/JPL-Caltech/ESA/Herschel.
  
What lurks at the centre of our galaxy, the Milky Way? It&amp;rsquo;s a big question with an even bigger answer. Supermassive, in fact, as identified by Prof. Andrea Ghez and Prof. Reinhard Genzel. The two astronomers were key players in making the discovery: That a supermassive object lurks at the centre of our galaxy, likely a black hole.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
