<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3. We&#39;re In The Wrong Season on Quantized Crow</title>
    <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 3. We&#39;re In The Wrong Season on Quantized Crow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>As Beautiful As A Sunset</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/3/musicalbum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/3/musicalbum/</guid>
      <description>CW: Mention of the physical and sexual violence committed during the 1994 Rwandan Genocide.
 Photo of The Good Ones by Marilena Umuhoza Delli, Courtesy of Anti- Records.
  
The core members of The Good Ones are Adrien Kazigira, Javan Mahoro, and Janvier Havugimana. Each are a member of the nation&amp;rsquo;s divided social groups - Hutu, Tutsi, and Abatwa. The origins of the former two, Hutu and Tutsi, are incredibly controversial and ultimately a tool used to peddle conflict.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re In The Wrong Season</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/3/musicsingle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/3/musicsingle/</guid>
      <description>A still from the video of Black Rain, Copyright Loma Vista Recordings.
  
Peddlers of dreamy sex-groove, Rhye, have released their song Black Rain in preparation for the release of their new album Home. It&amp;rsquo;s a composition of all the best parts of their back catalogue: Mike Milosh&amp;rsquo;s trademark falsetto vocals, deep synth, and elegant strings. The song wonderfully changes tempo, switching between texture and speed whilst remaining groovy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electricity and Super Conductivity</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/3/scienceheadline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/newsletter/3/scienceheadline/</guid>
      <description>A magnet levitating above a supercooled superconductor thanks to the Meissner Effect. Credits: University of Rochester/J.A. Fenster.
  
As you read this, electricity is being channelled from its source and into your screen. This source is likely to be a turbine which is spinning in the heart of a generator somewhere, converting the mechanical energy of its rotation into electrical energy. Imagine it happening now. Imagine a hydropower plant like this one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
