<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>culture piece on Quantized Crow</title>
    <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/tags/culture-piece/</link>
    <description>Recent content in culture piece on Quantized Crow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quantizedcrow.com/tags/culture-piece/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jerusalem Lost I</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/oct21/jerusalemlosti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/oct21/jerusalemlosti/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;p align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;I.    Preamble &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’d driven to a nearby village with my friend Jake, who had come to visit. We passed a churchyard. There, above the low stone walls, stood a granite obelisk and fixed upon its surface was a large metal plaque adorned with the names of the war dead. These monuments are so ubiquitous that it feels absurd explaining what they are. They stand like stone antennae broadcasting a quiet signal that we’re all picking up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nourish I: Numbers</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/jun21/nourishi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/jun21/nourishi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;p align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;I.    Preamble &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;One day, Takeshi receives a letter informing him that he needs to return to hospital because of some worrying test results. He’s 60 years old and terrified of dying. His wife assures him that it’s nothing; he’s probably fine. Takeshi isn’t convinced. He hunkers over himself in the hospital waiting room. He doesn’t want to die.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Town Road: Yee Haw Utopia</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/jun20/old_town_road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/jun20/old_town_road/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A little while ago, I was having a discussion with my friends in which we attempted to identify the landmark moments in music that defined the last decade. One thing we all agreed upon was that &lt;em&gt;Old Town Road&lt;/em&gt; by &lt;strong&gt;Lil Nas X&lt;/strong&gt; was a cultural touchstone that careered though the musical landscape. This led me to return to the song.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
