<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Quantized Crow</title>
    <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Quantized Crow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jerusalem Lost I</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/oct21/jerusalemlosti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/oct21/jerusalemlosti/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;p align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;I.    Preamble &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’d driven to a nearby village with my friend Jake, who had come to visit. We passed a churchyard. There, above the low stone walls, stood a granite obelisk and fixed upon its surface was a large metal plaque adorned with the names of the war dead. These monuments are so ubiquitous that it feels absurd explaining what they are. They stand like stone antennae broadcasting a quiet signal that we’re all picking up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nourish I: Numbers</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/jun21/nourishi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/jun21/nourishi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;p align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;I.    Preamble &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;One day, Takeshi receives a letter informing him that he needs to return to hospital because of some worrying test results. He’s 60 years old and terrified of dying. His wife assures him that it’s nothing; he’s probably fine. Takeshi isn’t convinced. He hunkers over himself in the hospital waiting room. He doesn’t want to die.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Berman: Amidst American Water, Part II</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/mar21/amidst_american_water_ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/mar21/amidst_american_water_ii/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paula Crossfield:&lt;/strong&gt; Before we were talking about your process. In particular you were talking about &amp;ldquo;Smith and Jones&amp;rdquo; - looking at it as a way to describe your writing process.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Berman: Amidst American Water, Part I</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/dec20/amidst_american_water/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/dec20/amidst_american_water/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paula Crossfield:&lt;/strong&gt; Hi, David?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;David Berman:&lt;/strong&gt; Hey Paula.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PC:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you so much for taking the time and for getting back to me so quickly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art or Artist? Questions for a Scene</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/oct20/art-or-artist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/oct20/art-or-artist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daniel Johnston&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;rsquo;s most famous single piece of work is his album &lt;em&gt;Hi, How Are You&lt;/em&gt;. It was recorded in his brother&amp;rsquo;s garage and features a makeshift recording apparatus made from a chord organ and a couple of tape recorders strapped to a weight bench. Johnston started out as a musical scavenger, shrugging off structure he completely disregarded convention to create something unique in this album. The result is songs like &amp;ldquo;Big Monkey Business&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Walking The Cow&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Hey Joe&amp;rdquo; that absolutely lie on the right side of lo-fi genius.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Town Road: Yee Haw Utopia</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/jun20/old_town_road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/jun20/old_town_road/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A little while ago, I was having a discussion with my friends in which we attempted to identify the landmark moments in music that defined the last decade. One thing we all agreed upon was that &lt;em&gt;Old Town Road&lt;/em&gt; by &lt;strong&gt;Lil Nas X&lt;/strong&gt; was a cultural touchstone that careered though the musical landscape. This led me to return to the song.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trouser Economics</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/dec19/trouser_economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/dec19/trouser_economics/</guid>
      <description>This article was previously published in Incite Journal and The Guildford Dragon.
 A few weeks ago I was adrift amongst the aisles of Marks &amp;amp; Spencer. I don’t get paid very much, my rent is high, and my trousers had rips in all the wrong places. I was contemplating whether or not I could justify buying a new pair. I decided that I could proceed in three ways:
 Save money and continue wearing my old clothes as they slowly deteriorate until I emerge naked from my rags like a grotesque butterfly, Buy the jeans and reduce my weekly food shop by making vast quantities of soup, or; Abandon society, live in the hills and build a new society with the squirrels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alien Aurorae</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/dec17/alien_aurorae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 23:39:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/dec17/alien_aurorae/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I’m sure you know, the Sun is a bundle of particles experiencing incredibly high levels of heat, gravity, and confusion. This provides a situation that is hectic to say the least. And so, just like your average Joe, to blow off steam the Sun will occasionally blow off an unimaginable amount of charged plasma. The charged particles that constitute this plasma radiate out from the Sun and hurtle towards the orbiting planets. The charged particles that reach Earth have our magnetosphere to contend with. The Earth’s magnetosphere is strong for our planet’s size, this is thanks to its abnormally large iron core. The clash between magnetosphere and charged particles results in one of the most deeply beautiful performances to be observed on our world: the aurorae.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scattered Colours of the Sky</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/oct17/scattered_colours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/oct17/scattered_colours/</guid>
      <description>As I’m sure you’re aware the sky is blue, clouds are white, and sunsets are red.
Why does this happen?
The Earth’s atmosphere is 78% Nitrogen, 21% Oxygen, a pinch of Argon and then a sprinkling of various other gases. So, our atmosphere is mostly Nitrogen and Oxygen, and the atoms of these gases generally like to wander around in twos. This is what we call a molecule, and both molecules are joined by a chemical bond that is about 300 picometres long (tiny!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If It Looks Like A Duck</title>
      <link>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/jan17/like_a_duck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantizedcrow.com/posts/jan17/like_a_duck/</guid>
      <description>As science continues to bound through the 21st century, its frontiers stretch ever further towards distant conceptual horizons. The borders dividing the nations of science become increasingly distorted in the lands that inhabit these distinctly foreign frontiers. One region that inspires deep trepidation in the researchers who explore this realm, and endless suspicion from their colleagues, is where quantum mechanics crashes into systems biology to create quantum biology. Research into this tectonic collision of physics and biology began relatively recently, and is raising eyebrows across both fields.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
